The other the immersion idea that comes
to the experiment is that objects will
take on frequency and thus
move to the location representative of
that frequency.
Yes.
Because it's representative of that
object in that location.
I understand.
Isn't that exactly what gravity does? I
mean, right now our scientists talk
about gravity in terms of warping space
and thus objects move to the location.
from one perspective, that isn't
incorrect, but it's not the whole
picture. You're still seeing just a side
effect of the relationship
of frequencies with each other and the
relationship of geometry with itself in
certain patterns.
Like let's take a massful object like a
a neutron star, highly dense collection
of mass.
Yes.
It has a highly coherent gravity wave
radiation because there's a lot of
matter in one area.
Yes. That radiates out and any object in
its vicinity
takes on that frequency and it and as
such it it's drawn in.
Yes.
So that's the mechanism of gravity,
isn't it?
Yes.
That's it. It's just information.
the locational variables within objects
because it is powerful enough to do so.
Right. It's all the
enough to overwhelm the idea of their
initial locational signature.
And the objects around like a sun or a
star, whatever,
Yes.
they also take up the vibrations of
those around them and they wobble around
a little bit.
So this interactive exchange.
Yes, fundamentally it is an exchange of
information. That's what gravity is.
I knew it.
I Well, congratulations.
think about this every day.